Hi  there,  Adrian  here.  You  can
call  me  Rai  for  short.  So
let  me  show  you  the  AI
social  media  receptionist  that  I  built
for  one  of  my  previous  clients.
So  this  is  for  a  dermatology
fellowship  company  that  trains  physicians,  NPs
and  PAs.  They  were  losing  leads
in  Instagram  and  Facebook  comments  and
DMs.  So  I  built  a  system
that  captures  those  and  converts  them
into  a  book  called  24 -7.
And  I'll  show  you  this  live,
both  entry  points.  So  this  is
the  Instagram  page  that  I'm  going
to  show  you.  Example.  We're  going
to  comment.  I'm  interested.
Then  I'm  going  to  show  you
the  conversation  on  the  high  level
side.  Commented  triggered.
Opportunity  was  created.  And  for  a
few  seconds,  it  will  send  a
message  to  the  sample  lead.  Great.
We  saw  it.  And  then  you
can  see  there's  a  message  by
the  AI.  We  saw  your  comment.
You  commented  on  our  post.  So
it  looks  like  something  not  an
AI  made.  Right.  And  I'm  going
to  show  you  that  it  will
also
reflecting  on  the  message.  So  you
can  see  here.  Right.  And  then
from  here,  I'm  going  to  try
to  use  different  sample  messages  to
show  that  it  will  read  the
knowledge  base  and  the  context  of
the  business.  Right.  Okay.
It  takes  a  few  seconds.  10
to  20  for  now.  It  can
still  be  improved  depending  on  the
business  knowledge  base.  So
here  it  runs  on  the  back
end  as  well.  And  after  a
few  seconds,  it  says  this  message.
And  it's  asking  for  a  phone
number.  I  will  put  the  phone
number  even  in  an  incorrect  formatting.
And  I'm  going  to  show  you
that  it  will  also  be  updated
on  the  CRM  back  end.  Okay.
It  says  here,  as  you  can
see,  there's  no  phone  number  since
this  is  a  social  media  lead.
And  let's  wait  for  it  to
be  updated  by  the  AI.  Okay.
Let's  wait  for  it.  Here.
Let's  look  up  here.  Alright.
As  you  can  see,  the  phone
number  was  updated.  And  one  last
thing,  the  most  important  part  as
well,  that  it  can  be  updated
as  we  provided.  And  then,  let's
try  to  test  the  email  address
as
well  if  it  will  update  the
email.  Since  it's  also  important  that
it  updated  the  phone  number.  Right.
So  you  can  see  the  phone
number  was  updated.  And  one  last
thing,  the  most  important  part  as
well,  that  it  can  escalate  or
move  the  stage  on  the  pipeline
to  the  coordinator.  So
here,  I  will  show  you  that
it  will  be  moved  to  Handoff
and  Michelle.  Right  there.  Right.  I
didn't  put  anything  or  do  anything
manually.  And  it  was  transferred  or
moved  to  the  right  stage.  Right.
Which  will  really  help  for  coordinators
to  see  only  the  leads  that
are  ready  to  go.  Okay.  And
also,  the  AI  mentioned  that  it
will  reach  out.  Coordinator  will  reach
out  to  them.  Okay.  So  now,
let's  try  a  different  approach  which
is  direct  live  chat.  Okay.  So
here.  Alright.  Hello.  Now,
I'm  going  to  show  you  the
other  trigger  which  is  if  they
send  the  message  directly  from  your
Facebook  or  Instagram  page.  Alright.  Let
me  close  this  down  and  send
a  new  message.  Hi.  I'm  interested.
Let  me  try  that  one  even
if  it's  a  little  bit
typoed.  And  let's  see  how  the
AI  will  respond.  It  takes
5  to  20  max  seconds  before
the  AI  replies.  Alright.
Let's  see.  Alright.
So  again,  it  will  ask  directly
the  phone  number  so  it  will
be  prepared  to  the  phone  number.
Okay.  Let's  just  click  on  the
link.  Let's  try  a  different  number.
And  go  again  to  high  level.
So  you  can  see  phone  number
is  provided.  And  check  the  CRM.
We  will  also  update  the  phone
number.
And  yeah,  that's  it.  And  also
the  email.  It  also  can  give
the  information  about  the  price.  Depending
on  the  knowledge  base,  we  can
put  it  on  the  document.  So
it  will  be  read  and  we
can  update  it  right  away,  anytime
while  it's  running  live.  Right?  It
also  has  an  automation  logs  through
Slack  whenever  we  receive  an  output
that  is  not  correct  or  we
get  an  API  error  limits  from
the  CRM.  Right?  Yeah.  So  that's
it.  Thanks  so  much  for  watching
and  have  a  good  one.  It
has  been  great.  Oh,  seems  so
much  for  watching.  So  I'll  let
you  know.  We  won't  do  the
interview  on  the  radio,  I've  seen
you  trên  Franklin.  Now  where  you
are  not  going  on.  Thank  you.